beampulse.com 2016-05-05

# Privacy - BeamPulse

### Version 3 – 1st Januar 2013

www.beampulse.com is operated by BeamPulse SAS, 27 rue Victor Schoelcher, 68057, Mulhouse, France

If, at any time, you have questions or concerns about our privacy practices, please feel free contact us at contact@beampulse.com.

In this Privacy Policy references to « we », « us » and « our » are to BeamPulse.

**What information we collect and how**

The information we collect includes:

1\. Site Activity Data: Each time a visitor comes to this website, we collect and log certain information for a reasonable period of time. This information includes, but is not restricted to your machine’s TCP/IP address, date, time and the BeamPulse web pages you’ve accessed. We also collect information about the ‘referrer’ if you clicked on an external link that led you to our website. The information we collect is used solely for performance, site administration and security reviews. They are not sold or shared in any way with third party organisations.

2\. Cookies: We use analytics tools to anonymously analyse site usage enabling us to continually improve our site to provide the best experience to you, the visitor. These external sites may use a cookie to understand user behaviour. We currently operate an implied usage policy for cookies which means we assume you are happy with this usage. If not, you can change your cookie settings within your browser at any time. If you do not know what cookies are, or how to control or delete them, we recommend you visit [http://www.aboutcookies.org](http://www.aboutcookies.org/) for detailed guidance. Please note that not accepting cookies may negatively affect performance and other functionality across the site.

3\. Personal Information: Personal information such as your name, mailing address, email address or telephone number is collected only when you voluntarily provide it. Such information is received when you send an email through the site or make some other specific contact, such as completing an online form or registering to receive notifications. The personal information you provide is forwarded only to the person(s) equipped to handle your request and is used only to respond to your inquiry, unless you opt in to receiving further communications. In this case these communications come solely from BeamPulse and we will only send communications as defined by you. Personal information will not be sold or shared with any third parties.

Any changes to our privacy policy will be communicated on this website. Policy changes will not alter how we handle previously submitted personal information.

**Copyright**

Images, text, software, documentation, electronic text and image files, audio and video files and clips, and other materials on the BeamPulse website are protected by copyright laws and may be covered by other restrictions as well. BeamPulse retains all rights, including copyright, in data, image, text, and any other information contained in these files. BeamPulse expressly prohibits the copying of any protected materials on this website, except for the purposes of fair use as defined in copyright laws and as defined below.

**Linking**

BeamPulse’s website may link to other sites. We are not responsible for the accuracy or reliability of the content on third party websites, nor do we necessarily endorse the sites and their content.

If you would like your website to be considered for linking on the BeamPulse website, please contact us. We are under no obligation to provide reciprocal links and reserve the right to be selective in our linking practices.

**Contacting BeamPulse  about Privacy**

If you have any questions about our privacy statement, please contact:

BeamPulse, 27 rue Victor Schoelcher, 68057, Mulhouse, France.
